<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Manchester City Squad Players</string>

    <string name="player_name">Name</string>
    <string name="player_description">Description</string>
    <string name="about">About Me</string>
    <string name="about_name">Nur Muhammad Himawan</string>
    <string name="about_email">muhammad.himawan73@gmail.com</string>
    <string name="detail_name">Name</string>
    <string name="detail_nationality">Nationality</string>
    <string name="detail_description">Description</string>
    <string name="share">Share</string>

    <string-array name="players_name_data">
        <item>Pep Guardiola</item>
        <item>Ederson</item>
        <item>Stefan Ortega</item>
        <item>Scott Carson</item>
        <item>Kyle Walker</item>
        <item>Ruben Dias</item>
        <item>John Stones</item>
        <item>Nathan Ake</item>
        <item>Josko Gvardiol</item>
        <item>Manuel Akanji</item>
        <item>Rico Lewis</item>
        <item>Mateo Kovacic</item>
        <item>Jack Grealish</item>
        <item>Rodri</item>
        <item>Kevin De Bruyne</item>
        <item>Benardo Silva</item>
        <item>Phil Foden</item>
        <item>James McAtee</item>
        <item>Matheus Nunes</item>
        <item>Oscar Bobb</item>
        <item>Ilkay Gundogan</item>
        <item>Erling Haaland</item>
        <item>Savinho</item>
        <item>Jeremy Doku</item>

    </string-array>

    <string-array name="players_nationality_data">
        <item>Spain</item>
        <item>Brazil</item>
        <item>Germany</item>
        <item>England</item>
        <item>England</item>
        <item>Portugal</item>
        <item>England</item>
        <item>Netherlands</item>
        <item>Croatia</item>
        <item>Switzerland</item>
        <item>England</item>
        <item>Croatia</item>
        <item>England</item>
        <item>Spain</item>
        <item>Belgium</item>
        <item>Portugal</item>
        <item>England</item>
        <item>England</item>
        <item>Portugal</item>
        <item>Norway</item>
        <item>Germany</item>
        <item>Norway</item>
        <item>Brazil</item>
        <item>Belgium</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="players_description_data">
        <item>Pep Guardiolas rise from Barcelona B Head Coach to UEFA Champions League winner unfolded against a very different footballing landscape from the one he has since shaped at Manchester City. Following an era where counter-attacking football dominated, Guardiola showed there was another way. At Barcelona, he won La Liga three times and the Champions League twice, in addition to numerous other trophies including the Supercopa de Espana, Copa del Rey, UEFA Super Cup, and FIFA Club World Cup. His move to Bayern Munich in 2013 raised eyebrows, but he quickly improved an already successful squad, taking Bayern to three Bundesliga titles, two league and cup doubles, and three Champions League semifinals. At City, Guardiola made an immediate impact, winning his first 11 games and guiding the team to a record-breaking Premier League title in his second season. He won multiple Manager of the Year awards, led City to further Premier League and Carabao Cup titles, and took them to their first Champions League final in 2021. Guardiola continued to build on his success, winning more domestic trophies and securing Citys fourth Premier League title in five years in 2021/22. In 2023, he reached 100 home Premier League wins and guided City to a historic Treble, winning the Premier League, FA Cup, and Champions League. Guardiola further led City to its first UEFA Super Cup and another FIFA Club World Cup victory in December 2023, solidifying his legacy as one of the most influential managers in modern football.</item>
        <item>Ederson Santana de Moraes, known simply as Ederson, has established himself as a transformative goalkeeper since joining Manchester City in 2017. Beginning his career in Brazil at São Paulo FC, he moved to Portugal to join Benfica youth ranks, gaining professional experience with Ribeirão and Rio Ave before returning to Benfica, where he rose to prominence, eventually succeeding Julio Cesar and helping secure a league and cup double in 2016/17. Known for his remarkable reflexes and outstanding ball distribution, Ederson joined City at 23, quickly becoming a pivotal player in Pep Guardiola tactical system. In his debut season, he achieved 16 clean sheets, playing a significant role in City Premier League victory and earning a nomination for the PFA Young Player of the Year. His influence reshaped the role of goalkeepers in the Premier League, inspiring many to adopt a play-from-the-back style. Consistently excelling, Ederson has won the Golden Glove in multiple seasons, set the Guinness World Record for the longest drop kick in 2018, and was integral to City historic Treble win in 2023, which included the FA Cup, Champions League, UEFA Super Cup, and FIFA Club World Cup titles.</item>
        <item>Stefan joined the Club on a free transfer in July 2022 after his contract at Arminia Bielefeld expired. The experienced German bolsters Citys goalkeeping options and wears the No. 18 shirt. He started all but one of Arminia Bielefelds Bundesliga matches last term and made a total of 220 appearances during two different spells at a team he joined as a youngster in 2007. He made his first–team debut four years later, helping them win promotion to 2. Bundesliga in 2013. After joining TSV 1860 Munich in 2014, he made 64 appearances in three years before re–signing for Arminia Bielefeld in 2017, eventually becoming vice captain. Although he has the formidable talent of Ederson ahead of him, he played regularly in cup competitions and made several impressive displays. Stefan made his Premier League debut in May 2023, keeping a clean sheet in a 3–0 win over West Ham, which helped continue Citys positive run of form to secure a third consecutive Premier League title and his first English title in his debut season with the Club. The German conceded just one goal in the journey to securing the 2022/23 FA Cup after City overcame Manchester United 2–1 in the final. To top off his first season with City, Ortega Moreno was part of Pep Guardiolas Champions League winning squad that completed the Treble and created history at City. The goalkeeper was also part of the squad that traveled to Athens in August for the 2023 Super Cup, where the team beat Sevilla on penalties.</item>
        <item>The former England international goalkeeper signed a one year contract extension with the Club in May 2023, keeping him at the Club until the summer of 2024. Scott Carson originally joined Manchester City on a season–long loan deal on deadline day of the August 2019 transfer window and signed another season–long loan deal in September 2020. Starting his career at Leeds United, Carson joined Rafael Benitez Liverpool in January 2005 and featured for the Anfield side against Juventus in their Champions League quarter–final first leg. Loan spells at Sheffield Wednesday, Charlton Athletic, and Aston Villa soon followed, and his performances earned him a place in Englands 2006 World Cup squad as well as a permanent move to Tony Mowbrays West Brom in 2008. After three successful years at the Baggies, including helping them gain promotion to the Premier League in 2010, Carson moved to Bursaspor in Turkey in 2011. His form in the Turkish top flight earned him another England call–up, replacing Joe Hart for the second half of a friendly against Sweden in November 2011. Carson returned to England in 2013 to link up with Wigan Athletic before moving to Derby County two years later. He featured 30 times in the 2018/19 season as the Rams suffered play–off final heartache against Aston Villa. Carson has since brought his experience and knowledge to Citys goalkeeping department since he initially joined on loan in August 2019 followed by another season long loan in September 2020. He made his City debut away to Newcastle towards the end of the 2020/21 season, and in 2021/22 he came on for Ederson in the 0 0 draw with Sporting Lisbon. Since then, he has continued to be a valued voice and member of Pep Guardiolas team, sharing his expertise with Ederson and Stefan Ortega Moreno throughout the 2022/23 campaign. Carson was part of the City team named Premier League title winners for a third consecutive season in May 2023 and was also part of the FA Cup winning team in June 2023. To top it off, he was part of Pep Guardiolas Treble winning team after the 1 0 win over Inter in the Champions League final, lifting the Champions League trophy for the first time in the Club’s history. Continuing the success into the 2023/24 season, Carson was also part of Guardiolas squad that beat Sevilla in the UEFA Super Cup on penalties, winning the European showpiece for the first time in the Clubs history.</item>
        <item>Kyle Walker became Citys third signing of summer 2017, arriving on a five-year deal from Tottenham Hotspur and taking the number two shirt. The England international quickly made the right-back position his own, winning six trophies in his first two seasons. A product of the Sheffield United academy, he spent time on loan at Northampton Town before returning to Bramall Lane and impressing in the final few games of the 2008/09 season. Spurs moved for him that summer, and he immediately returned to Sheffield United on loan. After a strong start to the 2009/10 season, he was recalled to Spurs and made two senior appearances. Further loan spells followed at Queens Park Rangers and Aston Villa, but in 2011 he secured a place in the Spurs starting lineup as their first-choice right-back, leaving White Hart Lane with 228 appearances and winning the PFA Young Player of the Year in 2012 while being selected twice for the PFA Team of the Year. Since arriving at City, Walker has been a consistent presence, making his 100th appearance in the 2019 FA Cup final within less than two years. His debut season saw him win the Carabao Cup and Premier League, followed by the Community Shield and FA Cup in 2019. At the international level, Walker has earned over 70 caps since his debut in 2011, including a successful World Cup campaign where he played as a right-sided center-back. In the 2019/20 season, he made 42 appearances, showcasing his consistency and athleticism as a vital part of Citys defensive strategy. His performance peaked in the 2020/21 season, again featuring 42 times and regaining his England place. Although injuries limited him to 31 starts in 2021/22, he still played a significant role in another title-winning campaign. His early impact in the 2022/23 season was hampered by a groin injury, but he recovered in time for the World Cup, making three starting appearances and helping England reach the quarter-finals. Walker contributed greatly to Citys success, aiding in the club securing its third consecutive Premier League title and the FA Cup with a 2 1 win over Manchester United. He also played a key role in winning the Champions League, featuring as a substitute in the final against Inter. Starting the 2023/24 campaign strong, he captained City to its first UEFA Super Cup trophy in August, scoring a decisive penalty in the shootout against Sevilla. Walker signed a new contract in September 2023, ensuring his stay at the Club until the summer of 2026, and he further captained the team to victory in the FIFA Club World Cup in December 2023, winning 4 0 against Fluminense.</item>
        <item>The 2020/21 Premier League Player of the Season, Football Writers Player of the Year, and Etihad Player of the Season is Ruben Dias. When he joined City in September 2020 at the age of 23, fans had mixed expectations for the latest addition to the squad. Nicknamed Ruby, the Portugal international began his senior career at Benfica, moving from the youth team to their B side in 2015. After 55 league appearances, he made the jump to the first team, playing 91 league matches over four seasons. His commanding presence and strong winning mentality caught the attention of Pep Guardiola, who brought Dias in to strengthen Citys defense. His influence was immediate, helping secure a watertight defense that conceded the fewest Premier League goals during the 2020/21 season while also lifting the Carabao Cup for a fourth consecutive time. Dias continued to excel in 2021/22, often wearing the captains armband in Fernandinhos absence. Although muscular injuries in the second half of the campaign sidelined him for several weeks, he made 40 starts and played a crucial role in Citys successful title defense. After a solid start to the 2022/23 season, he was part of the Portugal squad that reached the quarter-finals of the 2022 World Cup, making four starting appearances during the tournament. Following the World Cup, Dias featured in nearly all of Citys Premier League matches, proving to be a key component in the teams ten-game unbeaten run, which helped secure the Premier League title for a third consecutive season. He played the entire FA Cup final against Manchester United, winning his first trophy in that prestigious competition. To cap off another remarkable season, Dias contributed to City making history by winning the Treble after a 1 0 victory over Inter in the Champions League final. He added his seventh trophy to his collection after City won the UEFA Super Cup at the start of the 2023/24 season, defeating Sevilla on penalties after a 1 1 draw. Dias also became a FIFA Club World Cup winner for the first time in December 2023, as City triumphed 4 0 over Fluminense in Jeddah.</item>
        <item>John Stones is a highly regarded English defender who joined Manchester City in 2016 from Everton, initially attracting attention for his ball-playing abilities and composure under pressure. Born in 1994 in England, Stones began his youth career at Barnsley before moving to Everton, where he made his Premier League debut at the age of 18. Since arriving at City, he has developed into a key player under Pep Guardiola, known for his defensive prowess, tactical intelligence, and ability to contribute to the teams build-up play. Stones has been instrumental in Citys success, helping secure multiple Premier League titles, an FA Cup, and a historic Treble in 2023. He has also represented the England national team, participating in major tournaments such as the UEFA European Championship and FIFA World Cup, earning recognition for his performances on the international stage.</item>
        <item>Nathan Ake is a talented Dutch defender who joined Manchester City in July 2020 from Bournemouth, showcasing his versatility and strong defensive skills. Born in 1995 in The Hague, Ake began his youth career at ADO Den Haag before moving to Chelsea, where he progressed through the ranks and gained valuable experience on loan at clubs like Reading and Bournemouth. At Bournemouth, he established himself as a key player, known for his aerial ability and composure on the ball. Since joining City, Ake has played an important role in the teams defensive lineup, contributing to their success in securing multiple trophies, including the Premier League and FA Cup. He has also represented the Netherlands at various youth levels and the senior national team, participating in major tournaments like the UEFA European Championship and FIFA World Cup.</item>
        <item>Josko Gvardiol is a highly regarded Croatian defender who joined Manchester City in July 2023 from RB Leipzig, marking a significant step in his burgeoning career. Born in 2002 in Croatia, Gvardiol began his professional journey with Dinamo Zagreb, where he quickly gained attention for his exceptional defensive skills and composure on the ball. His performances earned him a move to Leipzig in 2021, where he continued to impress in the Bundesliga and UEFA Champions League. Gvardiol is known for his versatility, being capable of playing both as a center-back and left-back, along with his strong aerial presence and tactical awareness. Since joining City, he has contributed to the teams defensive solidity while helping secure numerous titles, including the Premier League and FA Cup. Gvardiol has also been an integral part of the Croatian national team, showcasing his talent on the international stage during the UEFA European Championship and FIFA World Cup.</item>
        <item>Manuel Akanji is a Swiss professional footballer who plays as a defender for Manchester City, having joined the club in September 2022 from Borussia Dortmund. Born in 1995 in Switzerland, Akanji began his career at FC Basel, where he showcased his strong defensive capabilities and earned a reputation for his speed and ball-playing skills. He moved to Dortmund in 2018, where he further developed his game and became a key figure in their backline, contributing to the teams successes in the Bundesliga and domestic cups. Known for his versatility, Akanji can play as a center-back or right-back, providing tactical flexibility to his teams. Since joining City, he has played a crucial role in their defensive setup, helping the club secure multiple titles, including the Premier League and FA Cup. Akanji has also been an important member of the Swiss national team, participating in international tournaments such as the UEFA European Championship and FIFA World Cup.</item>
        <item>Rico Lewis is an English professional footballer who plays as a right-back for Manchester City, having risen through the clubs youth academy before making his first-team debut in 2022. Born in 2004, Lewis is known for his technical ability, pace, and tactical intelligence, which allow him to excel in both defensive duties and attacking contributions. His impressive performances at the youth level earned him recognition, and he quickly established himself as a promising talent within the club. Lewis made significant strides during the 2022/23 season, earning opportunities to showcase his skills in domestic competitions and contributing to the teams successes, including winning the Premier League and FA Cup. His versatility allows him to adapt to various defensive roles, making him a valuable asset to Manchester Citys squad. Additionally, Lewis has represented England at various youth levels, further solidifying his status as one of the countrys top young prospects.</item>
        <item>Mateo Kovacic is a Croatian professional footballer who plays as a midfielder for Manchester City, having joined the club in July 2023 after a successful spell at Chelsea. Born in 1994, Kovacic began his career at Dinamo Zagreb, where he quickly gained recognition for his technical skills and vision on the ball. He moved to Inter Milan in 2015, further developing his game in Serie A before joining Real Madrid in 2018, where he won multiple UEFA Champions League titles and domestic trophies. Known for his dribbling ability, passing range, and tactical intelligence, Kovacic has established himself as a key player for both his club and the Croatian national team, representing his country in major tournaments, including the FIFA World Cup and UEFA European Championship. At Manchester City, he continues to showcase his talent and contribute to the teams successes in domestic and European competitions.</item>
        <item>Jack Grealish is an English professional footballer who plays as a winger for Manchester City, having signed with the club in August 2021 for a record fee. Born in 1995, Grealish began his career in the Aston Villa youth academy, where he progressed to the first team and became known for his skillful dribbling, creativity, and ability to draw fouls. He captained Villa in the Premier League, showcasing his leadership qualities and earning a reputation as one of the leagues most exciting talents. Grealishs performances earned him a call-up to the England national team, where he represented his country in major tournaments, including the UEFA European Championship. At Manchester City, he quickly became an integral part of the team, helping them secure domestic titles and contribute to their success in European competitions, while his flair and attacking prowess continue to captivate fans and analysts alike.</item>
        <item>Rodri is a Spanish professional footballer who plays as a defensive midfielder for Manchester City and the Spain national team. Born in 1996, Rodri began his youth career at Atlético Madrid before moving to Villarreal, where he made his professional debut. His impressive performances earned him a transfer back to Atlético in 2018, where he quickly established himself as a key player. In 2020, he joined Manchester City, where he has become a vital component of Pep Guardiolas squad, known for his exceptional passing range, tactical intelligence, and ability to disrupt opposition attacks. Rodri played a crucial role in Manchester Citys success, helping the team secure multiple Premier League titles and the UEFA Champions League trophy. On the international stage, he has represented Spain in major tournaments, contributing to their quest for silverware and further enhancing his reputation as one of the top midfielders in Europe.</item>
        <item>Kevin De Bruyne is a Belgian professional footballer who plays as a midfielder for Manchester City and the Belgium national team. Born in 1991, De Bruyne began his career at Genk, where he helped the club win the Belgian Pro League before moving to Chelsea in 2012. His time at Chelsea was limited, leading to loan spells at Werder Bremen, where he showcased his exceptional playmaking abilities. In 2015, he joined Manchester City for a then-club record fee, and since then, he has developed into one of the best midfielders in the world. Renowned for his vision, passing accuracy, and ability to score goals from distance, De Bruyne has been instrumental in Citys success, winning multiple Premier League titles, FA Cups, and the UEFA Champions League. A key player for Belgium, he has represented his country in several major tournaments, including the FIFA World Cup and UEFA European Championship, further establishing himself as a vital figure in international football.</item>
        <item>Bernardo Silva is a Portuguese professional footballer who plays as a midfielder or winger for Manchester City and the Portugal national team. Born in 1994 in Lisbon, he began his career at Benfica, where he progressed through the youth ranks and made his senior debut before moving to AS Monaco in 2014. At Monaco, he played a crucial role in the teams success, helping them win the Ligue 1 title in 2017. In 2017, he transferred to Manchester City, where he quickly established himself as a key player known for his dribbling, creativity, and work rate. Silva has been part of a highly successful City side, winning multiple Premier League titles, FA Cups, and the UEFA Champions League. Internationally, he has represented Portugal in several tournaments, including the UEFA European Championship and the FIFA World Cup, contributing to Portugals success in winning the 2019 UEFA Nations League.</item>
        <item>Phil Foden is an English professional footballer who plays as a midfielder for Manchester City and the England national team. Born in 2000 in Stockport, Foden joined Manchester Citys youth academy at a young age and quickly rose through the ranks, making his first-team debut in 2017 at just 17 years old. Known for his exceptional technical skills, vision, and versatility, he has become a vital part of Citys squad under manager Pep Guardiola. Foden played a significant role in Citys domestic successes, helping the team secure multiple Premier League titles, FA Cups, and the UEFA Champions League. He has also represented England at various youth levels and made his senior debut in 2020, contributing to the national teams campaigns in major tournaments, including the UEFA European Championship. Foden is widely regarded as one of the brightest young talents in English football.</item>
        <item>James McAtee is an English professional footballer who plays as a midfielder for Manchester City and the England national team at youth levels. Born in 2003 in Salford, McAtee joined Manchester Citys youth academy at a young age and developed a reputation for his technical ability, vision, and creativity on the ball. He made his first-team debut for City in 2021 and has since been recognized for his potential and skill. McAtee has also been a standout performer for Englands youth teams, showcasing his talent in international competitions. In the 2022/23 season, he gained valuable experience through a loan spell at Sheffield United, where he further honed his skills in the Championship, helping his team in their pursuit of promotion. McAtee is regarded as one of the promising young talents emerging from Citys academy.</item>
        <item>Matheus Nunes is a Brazilian professional footballer who plays as a midfielder for Manchester City and the Brazilian national team. Born in 1998 in São Paulo, Nunes began his career at the youth academy of the Portuguese club Estoril Praia, where he quickly made a name for himself with his technical skills and ability to control the midfield. He moved to Sporting CP in 2019, where he developed into a key player and helped the team win the Primeira Liga title in the 2020/21 season. His impressive performances caught the attention of Manchester City, and he joined the club in the summer of 2023. Known for his versatility, energy, and passing ability, Nunes has the capacity to play in various midfield roles, making him a valuable addition to Citys squad as they compete for domestic and European honors.</item>
        <item>Oscar Bobb is a Norwegian professional footballer who plays as a winger for Manchester City. Born in 2003 in Norway, Bobb began his youth career at Stabæk before moving to the Manchester City academy in 2020. Known for his speed, dribbling ability, and creativity on the ball, he quickly made an impression within the youth setup at City. Bobb has represented Norway at various youth levels and was part of the squad that competed in the UEFA European Under-19 Championship. His performances in the youth leagues have drawn attention, and he is regarded as one of the promising talents in City’s academy, with aspirations to break into the first team and make an impact in the Premier League.</item>
        <item>Ilkay Gundogan is a German professional footballer who plays as a midfielder and captained Manchester City from 2021 to 2023. Born in 1990 in Gelsenkirchen, Germany, he began his career at VfL Bochum before moving to 1. FC Nürnberg, where he gained recognition for his technical skills and vision. Gundogan signed with Borussia Dortmund in 2011, winning the DFB-Pokal and reaching the UEFA Champions League final in 2013. In 2016, he joined Manchester City, where he has been instrumental in the teams success, winning multiple Premier League titles, FA Cups, and the UEFA Champions League. Known for his passing ability, tactical intelligence, and leadership qualities, Gundogan has also been a key figure in the German national team, representing his country in several major tournaments, including the FIFA World Cup and UEFA European Championship. In June 2023, he signed with FC Barcelona after leaving City, marking the end of an impactful era at the club.</item>
        <item>Erling Haaland is a Norwegian professional footballer who plays as a striker for Manchester City and the Norway national team. Born on July 21, 2000, in Leeds, England, he began his career at Bryne FK in Norway before moving to Molde FK, where he showcased his goal-scoring prowess. Haaland gained international attention during his time at Red Bull Salzburg, where he became the top scorer in the UEFA Champions League group stage in the 2019/2020 season. In January 2020, he signed with Borussia Dortmund, where he continued to excel, becoming one of the most prolific strikers in Europe. In the summer of 2022, Haaland joined Manchester City, where he quickly made an impact by breaking multiple goal-scoring records in the Premier League. Known for his incredible speed, strength, and finishing ability, he has established himself as one of the top forwards in world football. Haaland also represents Norway internationally, participating in major tournaments and qualifiers, showcasing his talent on the global stage.</item>
        <item>Savinho is a Brazilian professional footballer known for his attacking prowess and versatility on the field. Born on December 10, 2004, in Belo Horizonte, Brazil, he began his career at Atletico Mineiro, where he showcased his skills as a forward and earned attention for his speed and technical ability. Savinho made his professional debut at a young age and quickly became recognized as one of the most promising talents in Brazilian football. In 2023, he joined Manchester City, where he continues to develop his game and aims to make an impact in one of the most competitive leagues in the world. Savinho is considered a player with significant potential, and his performances have drawn comparisons to some of the top attacking players in football.</item>
        <item>Jeremy Doku is a Belgian professional footballer known for his explosive pace and skillful dribbling as a winger. Born on May 27, 2002, in Antwerp, Belgium, he began his youth career at Anderlecht before moving to Rennes in 2020, where he made a significant impact in Ligue 1 with his dynamic playing style. Doku gained recognition for his ability to take on defenders and create goal-scoring opportunities, earning him a reputation as one of the brightest young talents in European football. In 2023, he signed with Manchester City, furthering his development under a top-tier coaching staff and aiming to make a mark in one of the worlds most competitive leagues. Doku has also represented Belgium at various youth levels and made his senior debut, contributing to the national teams attacking options with his flair and creativity on the ball.</item>
    </string-array>

    <integer-array name="players_photo_data">
        <item>@drawable/pep_guardiola</item>
        <item>@drawable/ederson</item>
        <item>@drawable/stefan_ortega</item>
        <item>@drawable/scott_carson</item>
        <item>@drawable/kyle_walker</item>
        <item>@drawable/ruben_dias</item>
        <item>@drawable/john_stones</item>
        <item>@drawable/nathan_ake</item>
        <item>@drawable/josko_gvardiol</item>
        <item>@drawable/manuel_akanji</item>
        <item>@drawable/rico_lewis</item>
        <item>@drawable/mateo_kovacic</item>
        <item>@drawable/jack_grealish</item>
        <item>@drawable/rodrigo</item>
        <item>@drawable/kevin_de_bruyne</item>
        <item>@drawable/bernardo_silva</item>
        <item>@drawable/phil_foden</item>
        <item>@drawable/james_mcatee</item>
        <item>@drawable/matheus_nunes</item>
        <item>@drawable/oscar_bobb</item>
        <item>@drawable/gundogan</item>
        <item>@drawable/erling_haaland</item>
        <item>@drawable/savinho</item>
        <item>@drawable/jeremy_doku</item>
    </integer-array>
</resources>